game-monitor.com 2008-01-29

# Privacy Policy :: Game - Monitor . COM

**References:**

  * **Game-Monitor** refers to the Game-Monitor websites, and excludes its owners and operators.

**About:**

This is a privacy policy for [Game-Monitor.com](http://www.game-monitor.com/). The full text of Game-Monitor's privacy policy is available at [www.game-monitor.com/privacy.php](http://www.game-monitor.com/privacy.php)

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by e-mail at . 

**Collection and Use of Information:**

The following information is collected automatically on every page view: 

  * Full IP address 
  * Referrer (Last URL requested by the user)
  * HTTP Request Method
  * URL of requested resource

The purpose for collecting this information is: 
  * to help improve the Game-Monitor website
  * generate statistics on traffic trends
  * for diagnosis of problems and abuse
  * to distiguish traffic between users, bots and web services

We also collect e-mail addresses, names and PayPal account email addresses for the sole purpose of notifying users of their subscription accounts and status. When canceling your subscription with Game-Monitor, you also opt-out of these e-mails. Cancelation of your subscription can be accomplished via your PayPal account or via e-mail requests to: support@game-monitor.com. 

The data collected will be used solely by Game-Monitor and Game-Monitor agents, and will be stored indefinately or until a time we deem it of no importance. 

**Cookies:**

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. 

Game-Monitor makes use of cookies for user login into the Game-Monitor forums and client control panel. Cookies may also be used by third party advertising companies shown on the Game-Monitor site. 

**Third Party Sites:**

Links operating outside the [Game-Monitor.com](http://www.game-monitor.com/) domain name are operated independently and are out of Game-Monitor's control. As such, we are in no way responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites. 
**References:**

  * **Game-Monitor** refers to the Game-Monitor websites, and excludes its owners and operators.

**About:**

This is a privacy policy for [Game-Monitor.com](http://www.game-monitor.com/). The full text of Game-Monitor's privacy policy is available at [www.game-monitor.com/privacy.php](http://www.game-monitor.com/privacy.php)

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by e-mail at . 

**Collection and Use of Information:**

The following information is collected automatically on every page view: 

  * Full IP address 
  * Referrer (Last URL requested by the user)
  * HTTP Request Method
  * URL of requested resource

The purpose for collecting this information is: 
  * to help improve the Game-Monitor website
  * generate statistics on traffic trends
  * for diagnosis of problems and abuse
  * to distiguish traffic between users, bots and web services

We also collect e-mail addresses, names and PayPal account email addresses for the sole purpose of notifying users of their subscription accounts and status. When canceling your subscription with Game-Monitor, you also opt-out of these e-mails. Cancelation of your subscription can be accomplished via your PayPal account or via e-mail requests to: support@game-monitor.com. 

The data collected will be used solely by Game-Monitor and Game-Monitor agents, and will be stored indefinately or until a time we deem it of no importance. 

**Cookies:**

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. 

Game-Monitor makes use of cookies for user login into the Game-Monitor forums and client control panel. Cookies may also be used by third party advertising companies shown on the Game-Monitor site. 

**Third Party Sites:**

Links operating outside the [Game-Monitor.com](http://www.game-monitor.com/) domain name are operated independently and are out of Game-Monitor's control. As such, we are in no way responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites.
